imperfectparent.com 2010-06-21

# The Imperfect Parent || Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

The Imperfect Parent respects your privacy and will never release any personal information about you without your consent. 

When you visit one of our Web pages, our server automatically logs your Internet domain or address (IP address) and the Web location you clicked from, so we can tell how many people visit each page and how they find us. If you click on an ad, your "click-through" is recorded so we can tell advertisers how many people are responding to their ads. Neither of these procedures identifies you personally or collects any personal information about you. We do not and will not collect your name, E-mail address, or any other personal information without your consent. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under age 13.

The Imperfect Parent allows third party advertisers to serve ads on its website content, and these ad networks may use cookies to improve your online experience, including the display of more relevant ads. Through a tool created by the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://networkadvertising.org/), you may [opt out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) of several third party ad servers' and networks' cookies simultaneously.

On certain pages, if you choose to register for a contest, sweepstakes, newsletter, message board, or some other purpose, we may ask for personal information such as street and/or E-mail address, phone number, consumer preferences, etc. We do not and will not release any such information unless we have your consent, or we believe in good faith that we are legally required to do so or that there is an emergency involving personal danger. Nor will we use this information to contact you in any way other than what is expressly stated in the registration. 

The Imperfect Parent collects personal information when registering for our Community forums. The only information that is required is a unique username and valid email address. Your community profile will contain any information you place regarding your occupation, location, interests, and website. These options are all voluntary, and may be left blank if desired. You are also given a choice of whether or not to display your email address. The default option for this is "no".

On some of our pages we offer content or services by providing hyperlinks to other Web sites -- for example, Amazon.com. Of course these sites are not subject to our policies; we advise you to read their privacy statements. 

Given the nature of Web publishing, our privacy policies may change from time to time; any changes will be posted here as soon as they go into effect. 

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please write to [prescott@imperfectparent.com](mailto:prescott@imperfectparent.com).   

_Last updated 05/03/10_

"A diamond with a flaw is worth more than a pebble without imperfections." _\-- Chinese Proverb_
